FWD fast
minimum which is 200,000 per year for 2
[music] years
200,000 basic premium let's say
price
today price is 1.14 14
screen
14%. It's now 1.14. [music] What we will
do is divide 200,000 divided by 1.14
equals
175,000 units. So units
pay [music]
which is quarterly. Next payout is
February.
But before pay
or cost of insurance and monthly [music]
charges
value and now pay
number of units times the [music] payout
amount per unit
managers
payment history
very
[music]
pay out per unit or 5.83% 83% per year
invest
number of units
number of units 175,438
multiply 014574574
screen and [music]
payout is equals
so 2500
first
So [music] on the second year
200,000 that means 5000
[music]
but again
amount per unit.
Another question is yes
[music]
history since 2022 from the start from
the inception
quarterly payout clients
or somewhere else why not let your money
work for you and diversify
real estate other investments. [music]
So why not invest in FWD fast lane at
least insured [music] insurance
of your premium,000
[music]
1 million minimum life insurance and
this is for your family. What if
5 million life insurance?
[music]
Let's sit down
and I can give you other options
insurance protection. Hello, my name is
Pach Bashal, your finance glow bestie.
Let's grow and glow together. Bye.
>> [music]